VERONIKA GOLOVANOVA

WEB-DEVELOPER

E-MAIL: the veronika@rambler.ru **RESIDENCE:** CZECH REPUBLIC, PRAGUE

PHONE: +420775494689 **CITIZENSHIP:** RUSSIA, KRASNODAR

I am currently working as frontend developer and prefer not to stop and constantly learn new technologies. It is always important for me to write clear and clean code and reusable components. I have 5 years of experience in programming, of which 2+ in web programming.

SKILLS JavaScript, React, React Native, Redux, Redux Thunk, Node.js, MongoDB, PHP,

MySQL, HTML, React Router, SASS, Gulp, Webpack

AGE 27

LANGUAGES ENGLISH: INTERMEDIATE

CZECH: UPPER-INTERMEDIATE RUSSIAN: PROFICIENCY

EDUCATION

KUBAN STATE UNIVERSITY

BACHELOR OF APPLIED INFORMATICS

• 2011-2015

• Russia, Krasnodar

VYSOKÁ ŠKOLA FINANČNÍ A SPRÁVNÍ

MASTER OF MARKETING COMMUNICATION

- 2018-2020
- Czech Republic, Prague

WORK EXPERIENCE

SQL DEVELOPER

000 "ITM"

1/2015 - 12/2017 Russia, Krasnodar

- Software development for a wholesale and retail company
- Database development Firebird SQL
- Software development for Portable Data Terminal on TSDserver and ZOPEserver (Python, JavaScript)

WEB DEVELOPER

DevCom, spol. s r.o

3/2019 - 7/2019 Czech Republic, Prague

- Development of web pages for internal use
- Database development MySQL
- PHP (Import/Export files by Phpspreadsheet, connect to DB)
- Development of the interface part (JavaScript, jQuery, CSS, HTML)

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Actum, s.r.o.

8/2019 - 4/2020 Czech Republic, Prague

- Development SPA on React
- Development of business applications for use with Sitecore
- Participation in internal projects of the company for the development of PWA applications